{
    "id": "ec040b090d6f4b38a84e1678e2b978d2",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns and Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Jane is the woman …………. keeps giant lizards in the garden shed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fd548655dcd24b289751e97a4c252dbe"
        },
        {
            "question": "The person ……………… keeps giant lizards in the garden shed is Jane.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a4b27d139a4c4bab987242cd6bf98bc4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Giant lizards are ……………… Jane keeps in the garden shed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6b954e5bfbaa4b4a887f3318734fb9f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. Jane keeps in the garden shed are giant lizards.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "That",
                "Which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c67efa0293a34911adc01ce5d023593b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The garden shed is the place ……………. Jane keeps giant lizards.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6806848c34a64c0c81fce7ef0379cd66"
        },
        {
            "question": "The place ……………… Jane keeps giant lizards is the garden shed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b786de54c03a4013bff5117db095230e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The secretary is …………….. Mark is.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "95545a664c74409d8604153df6f12e19"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tuesday was the day ……………….. I went to London to meet James.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0110661656904e5fb41fbdfd2160cde3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The day ………………. I went to London to meet James was Tuesday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "when",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "57a0345455994ebfad550551a00450e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "To meet James was the reason …………… I went to London.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "why",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d354a3b4fe3a47028f3def76a4c045c8"
        }
    ]
}